Guide to the Shanghai American School Records: the Phoebe White Wentworth Collection of Shanghai American School History and Memorabilia
Yale University Divinity School Library
Shanghai American School Records: the Phoebe White Wentworth Collection of Shanghai American School History and Memorabilia
1911-2016
RG 132
Yale University Divinity School Library
15.5
(38 boxes)
During the WWII years 1941-1945, however, various spin-offs of SAS were organized by former teachers that kept the school going (under different names), including a school established in a Japanese internment camp. A final spin-off, the Private America School, continued the basic SAS curriculum until 1950 when the Communist government forced the school's closure. The Shanghai American School (SAS) was founded in 1912 for the purpose of educating the children of American missionaries, businessmen, and professionals. It was the culmination of years of work by the American community to create a school in Shanghai that would prepare its children to enter American colleges and universities. The school maintained operations until 1941 when most members of the American community were evacuated due to political tensions between Japan and the United States prior to Pearl Harbor. In 1946, after World War II, SAS was reorganized and maintained operations through commencement 1949 when the Chinese Communist army occupied Shanghai. A period of volatile political and economic conditions ensued, causing the school to close once again.
Shanghai American School
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Shanghai American School Alumni Association
Biographical / Historical
The Shanghai American School, a day and boarding school from kindergarten through senior high, was founded in 1912, primarily to educate the children of American missionaries. The school was open to the children of all American citizens living in China, however, and from its inception attracted students from the business and professional communities. Children of Europeans, able to handle instruction in English, also attended. SAS opened with 38 students. The school quickly outgrew its original site on North Szechuen Road and by 1918 a committee was established to purchase land and build a permanent school. Eventually land was secured at 10 Avenue Petain where the school opened on a new campus in 1923. By 1925, during the tenure of Charles L. Boynton, principal, enrollment reached 417.
SAS was incorporated in the District of Columbia in 1921. The Board of Trustees, based in New York, held the title to the property. The school was locally controlled by a Board of Managers in Shanghai, appointed by the Board in New York.
In 1926, Mr. Elam J. Anderson, Ph.D. was appointed as principal. The school continued to grow in size and stature under his direction and in 1931-1932, the final year of his tenure, enrolment stood at 595 with a staff of 43. In 1932, Henry H. Welles, Ph.D. was appointed as the new principal. Enrolment continued to rise under his direction and in 1934 it went above 600. During his five-year tenure, Welles focused on improving the school's academic standards to the level of the best American prep schools.
Life in China changed greatly in 1937 because of the Sino-Japanese War. Nevertheless, SAS remained open until 1941 when most Americans were evacuated from China due to the ongoing war and the mounting tensions between Japan and the United States. Reduced to 20 percent of its former size, the Shanghai American School officially closed after commencement 1941.
Though SAS officially closed after commencement in April 1941, a spin-off, organized by Frank W. Cheney and other former faculty, managed to keep the school going through 1942-1942 under the name of the American Private School, and through 1943 on the premises of the Community Church, under the name of the Community Private School.
Vestiges of the Shanghai American School even continued during 1943-1945 in a Japanese internment camp where hundreds of Americans remaining in Shanghai after the 1941 evacuations, plus many Britons and Dutch, were interned following Pearl Harbor. This school, known as the Chapei Civilian Assembly Camp School, under the leadership of R. J. McMullen, Frank Cheney, and Eric Schmidt, graduated classes in 1943, 1944, and 1945.
In September 1945 Cheney organized the Shanghai American Private School at the Community Church, which, in the spring of 1946, reoccuped the SAS campus. In September 1946, Thomas C. Gibb, a former SAS teacher, was appointed principal of the postwar SAS by the reconstituted Board of Managers of the Shanghai American School. The postwar school grew to an enrolment of about 500 in 1948, but closed after graduation in 1949 when Communist armies occupied Shanghai.
The final spin-off of SAS, the Private American School, located at the Community Church, and under the leadership of Val Sundt, former SAS vice-principal and teacher, continued the SAS curricula until commencement 1950, when pressures from the Communist government made it impossible for an American institution to continue.
Scope and Contents
The collection provides valuable insight into the American community in Shanghai as it went through nearly four decades of tremendous change. It complements the records of other American schools in China found in YDSL Record Group No. 209, China American Schools.
The collections is divided into two series: I. Records related to Shanghai American School and II. Records related to the Shanghai American School Alumni Assocation.
The Administrative/ Promotional Material within Series I documents how an American school overseas was organized and operated. This material also illustrates the school's and the community's commitment to living an "American" way of life in a foreign culture.
The extensive Publications of Series I, mostly produced by the SAS students, provide valuable insight into the daily life the young people in this community and their reactions to events that changed the face of China and the world.
The Collected Material of Series I includes recollections and scrapbooks that document not only the life of young Americans, but also of the missionary, business, and professional communities in the pre-Communist China. This series also includes materials collected by Phoebe White Wentworth and Angie Mills in the preparation of their history of SAS, Fair is the Name.
The Alumni/ae Records of Series II show how the SAS community maintained contact and remained vibrant after the dissolution of the school. Years spent at Shanghai American School were clearly a formative highlight in the lives of its graduates.
Materials added in 2010, 2011, and 2015 update documentation related to the Shanghai American School Association and include additional publications and correspondence related to the Shanghai American School, primarily relating to Shanghai American School in its post-World War II period, 1946-1950.
Arrangement
I. Shanghai American School
II. Shanghai American School Alumni Association
Children of missionaries -- China; Missions -- China -- Educational work
- Shanghai American School, Series I
  - Historical documentation, 1921-2003
    - Original collection
      - Prospectus, 1921-1928 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
      - SAS Admission Policies, 1927-1928, 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2-A)
      - Staff handbook, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4-A)
      - Student handbook, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Student handbooks, 1933-1940 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
      - Nooze editorial handbooks, 1933-1935 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Bulletins, 1931,1933-1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Bulletins, 1935-1941 (Box 1, Folder 10-14)
      - Promotional pamphlet "Caring for our own", ca. 1930 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Promotional speech by Charles Boynton, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Documents about incorporation of SAS, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 16-A)
    - Addendum - 2010
      - Letters from Elam Anderson re. becoming new principal of Shanghai American School (SAS), 1926 Jun (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Magazine and news articles written by Elam Anderson, 1929-1931 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Letter from Elam Anderson to parents, 1930 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence regarding book purchases, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - SAS Board of Trustees minutes, 1966 Nov (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence of SAS principal and Shanghai American School Association board members regarding donations to school, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - U.S. Department of States Fact Sheet re. SAS, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Parent Talk magazine and menu, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Addendum - 2011
      - By-laws of SAS and layout of grounds, 1921 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - SAS Bulletin, 1946 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Roster of Board of Managers, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Minutes of Board of Managers and Executive Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Announcement of re-opening of SAS, 1946 Sep (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Teachers' contract, salaries, etc. teaching and service staff, 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Excerpts of teachers' letters; enrollment figures for SAS and Peking American School; letter re. closing school, 1948 Nov - 1949 Sep (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Inventory of SAS library, textbooks, and other equipment, 1948-1951 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Lease of SAS property to East China Health Ministry (Heh Yun-Ting); letters and copies to Trustees, 1950 Apr-Aug (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Letters concerning property and final expenses of SAS; incl. by Frank Price, George Helde, 1952 Oct- 1954 Jul (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Articles re. SAS from Shanghai Evening Post and China Press Survey, 1948-1949 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Microphone engraved "Gift of class of 1948" (Box OV2)
  - Publications, 1917-1949
    - School literary magazine
      - Nooze monthly (commencement issue), 1924 (Box 2, Folder 17A)
      - Nooze monthly, 1928 Oct, Dec (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
      - Nooze monthly, 1929 Mar, May, Jun, Oct, Nov (Box 2, Folder 19-23)
      - Nooze monthly, 1930 Jan, Mar, May, Jun (Box 2, Folder 24-27)
      - Nooze monthly (Commencement issue), 1930 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Nooze monthly, 1930 Nov, Dec (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
      - Nooze monthly, 1931 Jan, Mar, Apr, May, Jun (Box 3, Folder 31-35)
      - Nooze monthly (Commencement issue), 1931 (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Nooze monthly, 1931 Oct, Nov, Dec (Box 3, Folder 37-39)
      - Nooze monthly, 1932 Jan, Feb, Apr, Jun, Nov, Dec (Box 3, Folder 40-45)
      - Nooze monthly, 1933 Jan, Feb, Mar, Apr, May, Jun (Box 3, Folder 46-51)
      - Nooze monthly (Commencement issue), 1933 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - School newspaper
      - Nooze, Vol. 1, 1921 Nov 15- 1922 Jun 5 (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - Nooze, Vol. III, 1922 Oct 1- 1924 May 22 (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - Nooze, Vol. IV, 1924 Sep 23- 1925 Jan 22 (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - Nooze, Vol. V, 1925 Nov 13 (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Nooze, Vol. VI, 1927 Jan 14- 1927 Jun 10 (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - Nooze, Vol. I, 1929 Oct 7- 1929 Oct 28 (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Nooze, Vol. IX, 1929 Nov 4- 1930 Apr 7 (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Nooze, Vol. X, 1930 Oct 8- 1931 Jun 4 (Box 4, Folder 60-61)
      - Nooze, Vol. XI, 1931 Sep 23- 1932 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - Nooze, Vol. XII, 1932 Oct 13- 1933 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - Nooze, Vol. XIII, 1933 Sep 14- 1934 Feb 2 (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Nooze, Vol. XIII, Feb. 9, 1934- June 14, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - Nooze, Vol. XIV, 1934 Sep 14- 1935 Feb 21 (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Nooze, Vol. XIV and Shanghai American, Vol. I- bound and complete (Box OV1)
      - Shanghai American, Vol. I, 1935 Jun 14 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Shanghai American, Vol. II, 1936 Jan 10- 1936 Apr 24 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Shanghai American, Vol. III (see also oversize), 1936 Sep 19- 1937 Jun 17 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Shanghai American, Vol. IV, 1937 Oct 25- 1938 Jun 16 (Box 5, Folder 70-71)
      - Shanghai American, Vol. V, 1938 Sep 16- 1939 June 13 (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Shanghai American, Vol. VI, 1939 Sep 20- 1940- Jun 13 (Box 5, Folder 73-74)
      - Shanghai American, Vol. VII, 1940 Oct 2 1941- Apr 17 (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - Shanghai American - various volumes in rolls (Box OV1)
        Scope and Contents
        Additional issues of the Shanghai American are in Series VI, Addendum -2010
      - Shanghai American, Vol. I, Vol II, 1946 Nov 1 (vol. I), 1947 Nov 7 (vol. II) (Box OV2, Folder 76)
      - Shanghai American, 1946 Nov - 1947 Jun (Box 27, Folder 9-11)
      - Shanghai American, 1947 Oct-Dec (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Shanghai American, 1948 Feb-Jun (Box 27, Folder 13-14)
      - Shanghai American, 1948 Oct-Dec, 1949 Apr (Box 27, Folder 15-16)
      - Shanghai American, 1946 Nov - 1949 Apr (Box OV1)
    - School yearbook
      - Columbian, 1916 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Columbian, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 77-78)
      - Columbian (as literary magazine), 1917 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Columbian, 1919, 1920, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 80-82)
      - Annual (as extended Nooze), 1924 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Columbian, 1925 (Box 6, Folder 84-85)
      - Columbian, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 86-92)
      - Columbian, 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 93-99)
      - Columbian, 1940, 1941, 1948, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 100-103)
      - Columbian, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Columbian, 1940, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 11, 12)
    - Miscellaneous publications
      - Special Nooze, 1930 Dec 3 (Box 10, Folder 104)
      - Sophomore Ace of Spades, 1931 May 4 (Box 10, Folder 105)
      - Sophisticator, 1931 May 5 (Box 10, Folder 106)
      - Tuning In, 1935 May (Box 10, Folder 107-108)
      - Tuning In, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 109)
      - Tuning In, 1938 Nov (Box 10, Folder 110)
      - Tuning In, 1939 Mar, May, Dec (Box 10, Folder 111-113)
      - Campus Chronicle, 1941 Jan, Sep (Box 10, Folder 114)
      - SAS Alumni Nooze, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 163)
      - SAS Presents - Alumni news, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - Collected Material, 1911-1995
    - Original collection
      - Programs
        - Play programs, 1922-1942 (Box 11, Folder 115-117)
        - Music programs, 1919-1940 (Box 11, Folder 118)
        - Commencement programs, 1917-1950 (Box 11, Folder 119-120)
        - Sports programs, 1935-1940 (Box 11, Folder 121)
        - "Ill Flows the Globe" written by Peggy Lou Armstrong and performed at Agnes Scott, Parody of "Il Trovatore", 1930 (Box 11, Folder 121-A)
      - Chronologically arranged material
        - General, 1911-1932 (Box 12, Folder 122-125)
        - International Student Fellowship, 1924-1931 (Box 12, Folder 126)
        - General, 1932-1937 (Box 12, Folder 127)
        - Collected by James Lobenstine, 1934-1935 (Box 12, Folder 128)
        - Assembly Times, newsletter of the Chapei Civilian Assembly Camp; information for evacuees, 1943-1947 (Box 12, Folder 129)
      - Personal accounts
        - Various authors, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 130)
        - "Infamous Horseback Incident at SAS", by Cora May Marriott Baldwin, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 131)
        - Scrapbook of Eunice Smith Bishop, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 132)
        - Crocker Family Personal History, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 132-A)
        - Remembrance of Alec Von Drachenfels (Box 13, Folder 133)
        - "Where the Cranes Fly: the Adventures of Edith F. Millican, M.D. in China 1943-1948", by Edith F. Millican, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 134)
        - "A China Childhood" by Pierson Parker, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 135)
        - Remembrances of Dr. Alonzo Peeke, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 136)
        - "Here I Made my Home" by Mildred Proctor, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 137)
        - Personal Diary of Mildred Proctor, 1923 Apr- 1924 Jun (Box 13, Folder 137-A)
        - "Living in China: 1905-1937", by Hugh Stocker, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 138)
        - "Shanghai Boyhood", by Allen Young, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 139)
        - "Lest We Forget", by Jean F. Craig, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 140)
        - "Lund: a Giant Dane in Asia", by J. F. Gossard (Box 14, Folder 141)
        - Scrapbooks (2) (Box OV1)
      - Memorabilia
        - Various SAS banners (Box OV3)
        - Bust of Juno newspaper clippings, reminiscences, 1917-1949 (Box 25, Folder 238-240)
        - "Bust of Juno," chapter from the book "The Other City," by John J. Espey, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 241)
        - "Bust of Juno" by Phoebe White Wentworth, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 242)
        - Bust of Juno photographs (Box 25, Folder 243)
      - Materials for Fair is the Name
        - Letters (Box 15, Folder 142-146)
        - SAS "Beginnings" questionnaire, financial information re. book, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 210)
        - SAS History Project, "Old School", n.d. (Box 23, Folder 211)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Classes 1917-1920, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 212)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Class of 1921, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 213)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Class of 1922, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 214)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Classes 1923-1924, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 215)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Classes 1925-1926, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 216)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Class of 1927, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 217)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Classes 1928-1930, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 218)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Classes 1931-1934 (Box 23, Folder 219)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Class of 1935 (Box 24, Folder 220-221)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Classes 1936-1938 (Box 24, Folder 222)
        - SAS History Project, Corresp., Classes 1939-1942 (Box 24, Folder 223)
        - SAS History Project, Faculty (Box 24, Folder 224-225)
        - Early work on Fair is the Name (Box 24, Folder 226)
        - Work on possible illustrations for Fair is the Name (Box 24, Folder 227)
        - General source material for Fair is the Name (Box 24, Folder 228)
        - Sources consulted about info. for China, SAS (Box 24, Folder 229)
        - Introduction to Fair is the Name by John Espey '30 (Box 24, Folder 230)
        - "The Shanghai American School," first draft by Phoebe White Wentworth (Box 24, Folder 231)
        - Rough draft of chapter re. 1927, chapter on freshmen/senior years of Class of 1927 (Box 24, Folder 232)
        - SAS traditions (Box 24, Folder 233)
        - Information about SAS organizations and activities (Box 24, Folder 234)
        - Drafts of accounts of ASK life, 1932-1937 (Box 24, Folder 235)
        - Report on SAS History Project, List of donations of SAS material, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 236)
        - Nooze Source Material, 1933-1936 (Box 24, Folder 237)
        - History of SAS by Charles Boynton, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 147)
        - Charles Boynton papers from Hoover Institution, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 148-149)
        - Hoover Institution Archives list of holdings on Missionaries, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 150)
        - Information on post-war claim concerning S.A.S., 1970 (Box 24, Folder 151)
      - Other organizations and publications
        - American Chamber of Commerce, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 152)
        - Mid-China Mission (Box 16, Folder 153)
        - Newspapers, 1940s, 1950s (Box 16, Folder 154)
        - Community Church (Box 16, Folder 155)
        - Community Church (Box 16, Folder 156)
        - Physical Education News, 1939 Autumn (Box 16, Folder 157)
        - Shanghai's Schemozzle by Sapajou, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 158)
        - Newspaper Clippings, 1920s-1930s, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 159-161)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - Addendum -2015
      - Compilaton of newspaper clippings, articles, programs, 1924-1938, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - A Story of the Shanghai American School by Angie Mills: second edition - originally printed as Fair is the Name, 1997, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1912-1941, n.d.
    - Photographs, 1912-1923 (Box 26, Folder 244-245)
    - Photographs, Class of 1922 (Box 26, Folder 246)
    - Photographs from the collection of Elizabeth Wilbur Cressey '22 (Box 26, Folder 247)
    - Photographs, 1924-1937 (Box 26, Folder 248-250)
    - Photographs, Class of 1933 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - Photographs, 1937 -1941 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Faculty and staff, 1930's (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Senior High School photograph, Classes of 1933, 1934, and 1935, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 254)
    - SAS buildings, 1926-1936 (Box 26, Folder 255)
    - Campus and scenes around SAS (Box 26, Folder 256)
    - SAS buildings circa 1989 (Box 26, Folder 257)
- Shanghai American School Alumni Association, Series II
  - Organizational records
    - Original collection
      - Letters, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 165-166)
    - Addendum - 2010
      - How SASA started; Officers and advisors, 1989 Mar-Apr (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Working drafts of By-laws, 1989 Mar-Jul (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Ballots accepting By-laws, 1989 Apr (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Resolution of SASA Executive Committee amending By-laws and list of Class Representatives, 1989 Jul (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Memo to Executive Committee re. further amendments to By-laws, ballots, correspondence, 1994 Jan-Jul (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - Background information re. incorporation of non-profit corporations (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Working papers re. Tax Exempt ID#, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence with United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia re. proposed SAS Fellowship, 1990 Feb (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Minutes of Executive Committee: meetings 1-9, 1989 Apr - 1990 Jun (Box 28, Folder 25-27)
      - Minutes of Executive Committee meetings 10-14 and of General Membership meeting 1, 1990 Jul-1991 Mar (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - Minutes of Executive Committee meetings 15-23, 1991 May - 1995 Sep (Box 28, Folder 29-31)
      - Minutes of Executive Committee, 2005 Sep - 2008 Apr (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - SASA Newsletter
    - Summer 1989, and duplicate issues of later years, 1989-1997 (Box 17, Folder 167-168e)
    - Winter 1989, Spring 1990, Autumn, 1990, Winter 1990 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Spring 1991, Summer/Fall 1991, Winter 1991, Spring 1992, Summer/Fall 1992, Winter 1992 (Numbering of issues begins with Winter 1991 #8-11) (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Issues 12-17: Spring 1993 - Winter 1994 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Issues 18-21: Spring 1995 - Spring 1996 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Issues 22-25: Fall 1996 - Winter 1997 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Issues 26-27, 29: Spring 1998 - Summer 1999 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Issues 28, 30, 31: Fall 1999 - Spring 2000 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Issues 32-34: Summer 2000 - Spring 2001 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Issues 35-38: Summer 2001 - Summer 2002 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Issues 39-42: Fall 2002 - Fall 2003 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Issues 43-45: Spring 2004 - Fall 2004 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Issues 46-49: Spring 2005 - Spring 2006 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Issues 50-53: Summer 2006 - Summer 2007 (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Issues 54-56: Fall 2007 - Summer 2008 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Issues 57-60: Fall 2008 - Fall 2009 (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Issues 61-65: Winter 2010 - Summer 2011, 2010-2011 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Issues 66-71: Winter 2011-2012 - Summer 2013, 2011-2013 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Issues 72-74: Fall 2013- Summer 2014, 2013-2014 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Issues 75-80, 82: Fall 2014-Spring 2017, 2014-2017 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Alumni/ae Records, 1924-1997, n.d.
    - Original collection
      - Alumni Association
        - Membership directories, 1991, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 169-170)
      - Tapes
        - Tape recordings made at reunions, various years (Box 18, Folder 171)
      - American Schools in China- reunion information